<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travels &#8211; Geetra</title>
	<atom:link href="https://geetracom.local/travels/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://geetracom.local</link>
	<description>Providing Assured Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 13:52:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Most Affordable Places to Reside in Canada</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/most-affordable-locations-to-reside-in-canada/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15040</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To help you get the most bang for your buck, we’ve compiled a list of the most affordable places to live in Canada.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Luxurious Lodge in Tokyo Opening in 2024</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/best-luxurious-lodge-in-tokyo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=15034</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are travelling to Tokyo in 2024? find the best luxurious lodges that give peaceful and wonderful travel experience. In terms of luxurious motels, Tokyo has all the time been in a category by itself. So when Wayne Kask checked into the brand new Bellustar Tokyo, he anticipated a one-of-a-kind expertise. And that is precisely what [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top National Parks in US &#038; Accommodations</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/top-national-parks-in-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=11135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Top National Parks in US &#38; Accommodations Near me &#8211; Discover the beauty of the US top national parks. From the awe-inspiring Grand Canyon to the geothermal wonders of Yellowstone, explore breathtaking landscapes, abundant wildlife, and incredible outdoor adventures. Plan your visit to these iconic destinations and immerse yourself in the natural wonders of the United [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Affordable Travel Options in USA &#124; 5 Best &#038; Cheap Travel Options</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/affordable-travel-options-in-usa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 14:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=11129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Affordable travel options in USA can be a mystery. Several options exist if you wish to travel US affordably. To ensure a smooth journey, careful preparation is key. Start by exploring the various travel options available to you. This includes researching budget airlines that offer affordable flights, as well as considering the convenience and cost-effectiveness [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Best Road Trip Routes in US &#124; Road Trip Planner App</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/best-road-trip-routes-in-us-road-trip-planner-app/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 17:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=11123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you are looking to drive around major cities in United States? Here is the 7 best road trip routes in US, major routes in each states and approximate driving hours, and 10 best recommended Road trip planner app. Road Trip Planner App When embarking on a journey in US, several guides are necessary to [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Beaches in the USA for a Summer Getaway &#124; 10 Top Beaches in the US</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/best-beaches-in-the-usa-for-a-summer-getaway/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 12:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=11116</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you looking forward to move to the US and wants the best beaches to retire? here is 10 best beaches in the USA for a summer Getaway. Beaches with accommodation, clear water, fire pits, boardwalks, black sand, white sand, pink sand and lots more features. When it comes to the best beaches in the [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Find Cheap Accommodation in Canada for International Students 2023</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/cheap-accommodation-in-canada-for-international-students/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 15:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=11082</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Are you in need of cheap accommodation in Canada? You&#8217;ve come to the right place! This article provides valuable information on the most cost-effective housing options available for international students in Canada. As an international student, there are numerous housing choices to consider in Canada. Whether you prefer on-campus residences or off-campus apartments for rent, [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>52 Best Places to Visit in the USA</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/best-places-to-visit-in-the-usa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=14885</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It takes a while to streamline across the very largest locations in the United States because the country is home to such a vast range of regions, from scenic coasts to bustling metropolises. This article digests the best places to visit in the USA and considered several factors, such as attractions, lodging, food options, and insightful feedback from thousands of travelers, to pick the top locations. Check out the Best Hotels in the USA if you're looking for lodging.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Attractions in Edinburgh, Scotland &#124; Everything you Must Know</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/attractions-in-edinburgh-scotland/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=10921</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Explore the captivating attractions of Edinburgh, Scotland, and immerse yourself in its rich history and vibrant culture. From the majestic Edinburgh Castle and the Royal Mile&#8217;s historic landmarks to the picturesque Holyrood Palace and the enchanting Arthur&#8217;s Seat, there is something for everyone. Uncover the secrets of the Royal Yacht Britannia, marvel at the ancient [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calton Hill Edinburgh Attractions &#124; All you need to Know</title>
		<link>https://geetracom.local/calton-hill-edinburgh-attractions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Godfrey]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Travels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.geetra.com/?p=10945</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Discover the allure of Calton Hill in Edinburgh with its panoramic views, iconic monuments, and rich historical significance. From the top, enjoy breathtaking vistas of the city&#8217;s skyline, including Edinburgh Castle and Arthur&#8217;s Seat. Explore notable landmarks like the National Monument and Nelson Monument, and delve into the cultural events hosted on the hill. Calton [&#8230;]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
